I am right
that while purchasing a health insurance policy,
one of the most frequently
asked questions from the planners is
whether I should purchase my health insurance policy
from a standalone health insurance company or from
a general insurance
company. So, before
we purchase a health insurance policy from any company, we have to
see whether that
insurance company will stand by us at the time of claim or whether the
background
of that company is very strong because health
insurance policy is such a subject
for which the insurance company
needs a lot of liquid points because
in a health insurance policy, claims are expected from the debt itself. So
today we will talk about a very Shubh
Bank branch. If we talk about this brand, then
this brand is also associated with banking
and if we talk about the market cap, then
this company has a market cap of 989 in the general insurance sector. So today we will talk
about Health Shield, a very leading health insurance plan of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.  Hi friends, my
name is Deepak Jain and I am the founder of
Quality Again Selfie
ICICI Lombard Complete Health
Insurance. So friends, let's talk
about the health insurance plan in great
detail. So first of all, if we talk about the coverage, then the
cover types of minimum cover options are
available, a combination option of 5 lakhs
is available, insurance option of 7 lakhs
is available, 10 lakhs, 152 lakhs, 25 lakhs and up to ₹50000000
is available in this plan. Next, let's talk about
pain treatment. This is an inbuilt feature. The
benefit is medication and treatment by being
hospitalized for a period of 24 hours.
Moderate infection treatment means
that when there is admission in the hospital for 24 hours, only
then is the insurance admissible under the health insurance policy.
Next, let's
talk about Prayas Federation. Pre-
hospitalization is 30 days in this plan. If
you have sterilization for 60 days, then the medical
expenses  Thirty days included immediately before
and six days after hospitalization will be
covered.
If we talk about expenses, then
30 days of expenses before hospitalization and
selected six days after discharge are covered.
Islamic Plan covers the expenses. Now let's talk about
day care procedures and treatment. This is an
expense feature. All the medical expenses
included while undergoing procedures,
treatments which require a 24-hour stay.
Discover new
technological advancements of medical science.
Today's procedures have become
very advanced, due to
which there is no need to stay in the hospital for 24 hours.
Such
treatments now come under day care procedures. There is
no redefined list.
Unlimited one-hour procedures can be
used under this plan. Next, let's
talk about PD waiting period
declared and accepted. This is a will feature
and lasts for two years.  Let us understand the waiting period benefit
in detail and declared and
accepted pre-existing conditions are covered
immediately after two years of
continuous coverage under the policy and
policies issued for the first time with
ICICI Lombard can reduce the waiting period by two years. Should have been quite a
similar
policy before opting for this policy
subject to Highway-12 Portability Regulations
to PDF. If we talk about the waiting period, then there is a
waiting period of 2 years, that is,
if you are purchasing a pre-existing policy from the company
and you declare any pre-existing
problem that you have and the
company accepts it, then that
coverage will be covered after two years of taking the policy. In
this way, if we
talk about portability case, then in
portability case, if your policy is
already running then there will be no waiting period in it, that is, the
waiting period in it becomes 10 years.
Next, let us talk about
in-patient  If we are talking about AYUSH AYUSH hospitalization
then this is also an inbuilt feature, let us understand the benefit of
expenses and Ayurveda, Yoga
and Natural Naturopathy, Unani Siddha and
Homeopathic AYUSH treatment only when it has been
undergone in AYUSH hospital and their
Tuesday care center and in reimbursement
piece, then inpatient AYUSH hospitalization will be
covered under this line but the coverage it will give you should be
only in AYUSH hospital
or AYUSH day care center,
in this Ayurvedic Unani Siddha
treatment is covered and if
you take this treatment then
you can claim it from the company only on investment basis,
next now let's talk about donor
expenses, there is investment feature over
and above all the best Sami should show,
if we talk about it then within the 5 lakh Sami discount,
up to the Sami discount, with you in the
lakh and 10 lakh option, there is
now a broken minute discount and in the discounts above that,
now 210 account
benefit we are including this  You can avail the
benefits in the plan. Medical expenses are
included in respect of the donor for any
of the organ transplant surgeries
provided. Organ donation is for the
richest person. Organ transplant expenses
mean that when a person
needs a body part on one side
and
this part is removed from one body and implanted in another body, the
best thing about this feature is that if you
read here, then over and above all the best,
except for the lack of, this benefit is being covered above the sum insured. For example,
if we explain it by looking at an example, if you have a policy of ₹5, then the additional
expenses of the organ donor of Rs 15 lakh will be
covered in this plan. Next, let us talk about the
Unlimited Reset Benefit, this is also an
inbuilt feature. We understand that the benefit will reach up
to 100% of the best Tamil Nadu
unlimited time Cinepolice year in case of
Mother in small including additional
commission, dip family to no claim bonus, a
funny and some insured protector of
feminism in speed as a result of
previous claim in the policy, either
unlimited reset benefits are within the plan, let's
understand it by example, if
you have a policy of ₹1000000 and if you get
admission, then the claim for admission is
of eight lakh rupees, you will get the
full level, you also start
and if you get admission and the
cost for that admission is ₹1200000,
then you can claim 10:00 from the company, if
admission is done again for the third year and
if there is an addition for the third time and the
cost in that fort is eight lakh rupees, then
if you mean that you can
use unlimited reset benefit within this plan,
next we will talk about dormitory
hospitalization, so  This is also an inbuilt
feature. Coverage for medical expenses in a
situation where the in-patient is in a
critical condition and cannot move to the
hospital and the treatment is done through home connectivity.
If we talk about the capabilities of the room in the hospital, staff salary, fertilization, then these are the expenses. If
treatment is done while staying at home, then this feature works.
If we talk about it, then this can happen in two ways. During
orbit,
we had seen that there were
no big hospitals available in our vicinity.
In such a situation, the treatment done
while staying at home is covered. Secondly, if we talk about the
patient being in such a condition that
he cannot be admitted to the hospital, then also the
domiciliary hospitalization feature
works. If we talk about air
ambulance cover, then this is also an investment feature.
If we talk about over and above the best means all left, then the coverage is
up-to-the-minute short for a good balance
pencil equal to transferring the short  Person
following emergency to the nearest
hospitals, the charges of air ambulance will be
covered in this plan, ok now cover up
to 10 chillies and that means the expenses of
taking the patient to a nearest hospital by air, if we
talk about SI
protector then this is also an investment feature, if
we understand the benefits of such protector then such a promise is made, customer shall
not be impacted any one claim and
multiple claims admissible in the previous
year did not act the overall amount of
rupees six
times benefits available for certain mode of
type like and about SI protector,
if you understand it in very simple words then the
company gives you tempo
center no claim bonus in every claim premium, inside this SI
protector the company tells you
that if you have taken a trouble of 50 thousand rupees
then the bonus which you are getting
or will get will not be affected by any infection, that is
you will get a no claim bonus
So here I will tell you one more thing
that on every claim premier the company
gives you tempo stand bonus and
in every Akram year when your tempo
is owned it is added but if you have an
indebted property of less amount
then in such a case the company will
not use your bonus and will give you that bonus also. Let us
address that
additional sum except this, this is an inbuilt
feature and additional commission tempo stand
of annual sum should be provided on between Rs.
for every claim premier up to a
maximum of 50%. So we have already
discussed that on every claim premier the
company gives you tempo stand no claim bonus
and this is its maximum
limit, it can go up to 50%. So next let us
talk about emergency services like
domestic road ambulance,
ambulance assistance, tele consultation, all these
three are an inbuilt feature and
if we talk about domestic road ambulance then 1% of sum
insured  1% of sum insured and for those who
leave sum insured above Rs.15 lakh,
incident on Rs.10000 ruby, then
consider the benefit, recorded on road
ambulance services will be covered with a single PAN, coverage
limit within the country is 1%, top 10 cm wide
to maximum of that, all the
four details of domestic road ambulance will be
covered in line as
shown on your screen according to different sum insured, apart from this,
ambulance assistance and tele consultation,
you
can also get assistance for ambulance by calling the company's call center
and can get tele consultation, so
next time we will talk about some value
added services which are now an
investment feature in this plan, so first of all health checkup
coupons, in this plan you get
online chat with medical practitioner, you
can avail the benefit of second opinion,
dietician and nutrition in consultation,
health assistance, so these are all inbuilt
features, its benefits will be discussed in more detail  Let's
understand the value added services like
free health check-up coupons, online chat with
medical practitioners, specialty consultation,
deliberation and nutrition in consultation, provide
information on offers related to
health care services, slide consultation,
Technosys medical equipment and for
mercy to print. If we talk here,
then the company has sent you an app
which is
also for all our clients. If you
also want to download it from Play Store, then you
can do so. The
name of that app is I Will Take Care.
If you download I Will Take Care, then
you can redeem health checkup coupons from the website. So at the same
time when you have the company
policy, at the same time the
health checkup titto punch is also sent to you. So the
best benefit here is that
for the checkup, it is not that
you will have to pay from your pocket first,
later you will have to get reimbursement. You can download the
company's app I Will Take Care at
any diagnostic center on that app,
which is inside it, on Press Friday,
non-stick  There are more prescribed tests from the center,
you can fix your health checkup through that
and can go there and get your tests done. The
company has added a very good feature of this in Oil Arpit Clear called Priya
Teacher and this feature is that if
you keep your face in
front of that app for 2 minutes, then
you will get six types of benefits in it, that is,
your BP, sugar and apart from this,
your oxygen level and in this way you will get six
benefits instantly, now it will
show you the complete details according to your current situation and if
you get all these tests done individually, then
you have to pay approximately
₹50 for each test, so if you also
want to see this picture, then you can
download iTech Care and use the benefit of this feature,
so next time we will talk about Hospital
Delhi, this is its optional Padman picture,
you can get ₹1000 or
₹2000  ₹3000 for D.El.Ed Western region
according to Ghee benefit, understand that the effective
amount of this father plant swelling will be paid
for each and every completed a swarm
optimization in search of digestion in
sacrifice for a minimum of three consecutive working
days and subject to a maximum of three days of tank
conducted. So,
if we can use the benefits between Hospital Delhi in such a way
that after admission, many times
we meet officer relatives of the patient, then the
expenses of their tea and water or other
basic small expenses incurred during the
stay in the hospital, then
you can cover those expenses through Hospital Delhi Cantt benefit,
so for this, but the minimum
condition is that there should be a minimum of 3 days
hospitalization and the maximum
company tenders for this, let's talk about it,
quit the conversation, this is also an optional
benefit and its maximum
limit is Rs.10000.  Let us
understand the benefit now. Benefit amount of Rs. 10,000
per inch and once during the policy period.
Bill paid in case of hospitalization
arising out of injury or illness cover
under the policy for a period of
constructive 10 days and Mode Shop Versus
Benefit is basically a feature which the
company says that if you are admitted
for 10 days, then it gives you this benefit to reduce some of your other
expenses like your job or
salary.
So this is an
optional cover which you can
add to your plan by paying an additional premium.
Next let us talk about the screen
protector, it also works as an optional don,
it is optional, you
can take it if you want or you can also take it, so
understand its benefits. Screen protector is for its
customers who are fit for discover the
IRDA's list of non-perishable
items will be compatible in case of  Classic
screen protector is a recipe. Have you
noticed that during the time of bed,
many doctors
used to use such materials which were
not covered in any health insurance policy.
But if you take out a plain protector, then there will be
no deduction in any way. If you take out gloves, pants or
any such non-performing item, then the company will
present all of them in your claim. Next, let's talk about
sum insured protector, this is
also an optional benefit. So let's
understand the benefit. If 10 customers have
opted for this cover, then the benefit will be increased on the basis
of inflation
rate of previous year.
If we talk about this short product, then
I will try to explain you with an example.
Suppose you had taken out a policy of Rs 10 lakh and
you did
not have any claim in that year, then the company will
give you a no claim bonus of 10 per cent.
What does the company tell you about the protector,
as you can see  You can say that every
year the government
declares the inflation rate, which the
steel
company tells you that whatever
inflation rate I have decided, I will give it to you in
addition, so as we
discussed the example, you
got 10 percent of no claim bonus for 10 lakhs and if there is a
six percent rate for support, then the
company will give you plus 60 percent, so next, let's talk about
super no claim bonus, super
no claim bonus, this is also an optional
cover, so if you talk about it, for
sum insured five lakhs and 10 lakh rupees,
then 50% of 50% increase in the sum
insured points, completed claim free up
to a maximum of 100 percent of best
means of, but if you turn off super no claim bonus
and if you have selected the option of 5 lakhs, 7 lakhs and 10
lakhs, then the
company will give you 50 percent of no claim bonus in fabric claim premium.  If it
gives claim bonus, then your
policy doubles in two years only, that is, if
you
purchase a policy of Rs 10 lakh from the company and
if you select the option of super no claim bonus, then
next year your policy will become
15 lakh and then in Dare that
policy will become 10 plus i.e. 20 lakh. Let's talk about
Swami, that is, if you
select above 10 lakh here, then you will get
completely free up to maximum 0 lakh.
This means that if
you
purchase a policy of
₹5000000, then the company will
give you a bonus of every year fee and your
policy will be of
maximum
₹50, which
you will get 50% everyday every year, that is, the
policy will become 500 crore in 4 years.
Next, let's talk about nursing home, this is
optional, daily it is ₹2000
₹3000 Pandey ₹3000. Positive person should be left,
understand the real  Name contest for
plants Gurjar positive for maximum up to two
parts poison for the medical services
staff nurses resident or
after discharge from the hospital,
if a nurse is called to the home in post graduation, then the
expenses up to 10 out of that for visiting the nursing home i.e. the nurse
's home, then that too will be covered
in the plant Review on gas and Aishwarya given the
updated benefits
Next now let's talk about compassionate visit,
this is also an optional don't benefit is
10,000 20,000 20,000 S semi wide
options available to benefit if we talk about in the
event of hospitalization one seat
Friday the cost of economy class air
ticket up to up redefined amount in Kakkar
Vada customers images family member boy
travelling to place of migration from the
place of original residence and back will be
rampables support that if the
person's admission person's
hospitalization happened  If the patient is travelling to some
other city far away, then a ninth class air
ticket will be given to him for going there
and returning from there to his
blood relatives for their take care.
So next, let's talk about critical
illness for adults only. This is also an
optional don't rider.
If we talk about its benefit, the customer can avail of critical
illness cover covering name specifically in less
medical procedures. Now the benefit amount speeds
up for diagnosis of the tuition created by the
tailor. So as soon as the critical illness is diagnosed,
in such a condition, whether you demand details or
not, you will get durdasha chilli and half included four
to fifty percent of the means and the person should have
options available for critical illness
chemicals. So, this amount will be covered on the
line. Next, let's talk about personal
accident.
This option is also available for adults only. It is optional.
Like don't rider, this plan also works
and this feature  This is what is insured
if we talk about Velvet then customer care no of
personal accident cover up Shikshamitra should
speed up on the
unfortunate event of accidental death of
permanent total disability resulting from
accidents policy details have been given by a courier company above the building
where if there is accidental death
here I have mentioned total disabilities and
disability that is if the hands
and legs of the body are lost then in such a condition
also the company remembers the line Durdasha Means Curd now so now there is
an
optional do not cover so
friends and today we discussed
about a very leading health insurance plan of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company health record
so we have discussed AIIMS and the product
with great clarity
and if you like this plan
then please share this video
with as many of your friends and relatives as possible so that
we can them  Be able to
become financially independent and if
you still feel that you
want to purchase a policy under this plan or
want to post your existing policy
then you
can coordinate with our team on the number written on the distraction
so friends thank you thank you so much for
watching the video thank you too